http://www.dentalmarketingcenter.com/privacy-policy/

Press enter to begin your search
Cutting Edge Privacy PolicyPRIVACY POLICY:Cutting Edge Digital Marketing (“Cutting Edge Digital Marketing“) operates cuttingedge.marketing and may operate other websites. It is Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Cutting Edge Digital Marketing collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Cutting Edge Digital Marketing may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Cutting Edge Digital Marketing also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on cuttingedge.marketing blogs/sites. Cutting Edge Digital Marketing only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s websites choose to interact with Cutting Edge Digital Marketing in ways that require Cutting Edge Digital Marketing to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Cutting Edge Digital Marketing gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at cuttingedge.marketing to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Cutting Edge Digital Marketing are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Cutting Edge Digital Marketing collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Cutting Edge Digital Marketing. Cutting Edge Digital Marketing does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Aggregated StatisticsCutting Edge Digital Marketing may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Cutting Edge Digital Marketing may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Cutting Edge Digital Marketing does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationCutting Edge Digital Marketing discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s behalf or to provide services available at Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Cutting Edge Digital Marketing will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Cutting Edge Digital Marketing discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Cutting Edge Digital Marketing believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Cutting Edge Digital Marketing, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Cutting Edge Digital Marketing website and have supplied your email address, Cutting Edge Digital Marketing may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Cutting Edge Digital Marketing and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Cutting Edge Digital Marketing takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Cutting Edge Digital Marketing uses cookies to help Cutting Edge Digital Marketing identify and track visitors, their usage of Cutting Edge Digital Marketing website, and their website access preferences. Cutting Edge Digital Marketing visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Business TransfersIf Cutting Edge Digital Marketing, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Cutting Edge Digital Marketing goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Cutting Edge Digital Marketing may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.AdsAds appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Cutting Edge Digital Marketing and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Cutting Edge Digital Marketing may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Cutting Edge Digital Marketing’s sole discretion. Cutting Edge Digital Marketing encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a cuttingedge.marketing account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.Client ReviewsRecent Projects
Cutting Edge 140 S Spriggs Blvd Bloomington, IN, 47403 United StatesText us or call anytime (317) 999 7733 hello@cuttingedge.marketing © Cutting Edge | Privacy | Terms |
Accepted | Marketing for Surgeons
What We DoServicesDental Marketing PackageDental SEOSurgeon Marketing PackageWebsite Design for Dentists & SurgeonsCertified Google Ads For Dentists & SurgeonsFacebook & Instagram AdsSpy Competing Medical PracticesSoftwareLead TrackerPractice Review PlatformMarketing DashboardOnline Dental Patient Registration PortalFree Instant Site AuditGoogle Update SensorNeural Machine TranslationsClientsRecent Clients & ProjectsLead Tracker LoginMarketing Dashboard LoginReview Platform LoginAboutReviewsDownload PricingWork With UsClient LoginLead TrackerMarketing DashboardReview PlatformTakeover FAQProjectsBlogContact8 Dental Website Design Essentials8 Top SEO Tips for DentistsDental Website Design CostText Us or Call (317) 999-7733
